pixelstalk.net 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy | PixelsTalk.Net

## Privacy Policy

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit **pixelstalk.net** , and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### **Server Logs**

As with most other websites, **pixelstalk.ne** t logs web, database, and other server-software usage and access information. This information may include your internet protocol (IP) address, which in many cases can be translated to an affiliation (such as your work, school, or internet service provider), or a geographical location. We only use this information for debugging purposes and for aggregating into anonymous usage and traffic statistics.

### **Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### **Contact forms**

We keep contact form submissions for a certain period for customer service purposes, but we do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.

### **Cookies**

While browsing **pixelstalk.net** , a small number of text files referred to as cookies are created on your local file system by your web browser at the request of our servers. These files allow us to personalize the browsing experience for users. You are free to delete them at any time or configure your browser not to create them. However, we do not guarantee that every feature of pixelstalk.net will function as expected without cookies enabled.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Use of Google Analytics. We use Google Analytics to collect information about use of the Website. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve the Website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with your Personal Data. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit the Website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use ](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html)and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to the Website by disabling cookies on your browser.

Google Analytics employs cookies to define user sessions, which allows for the collection of data about how visitors are using the Website. Google Analytics uses only first-party cookies for data analysis. This means that the cookies are linked to a specific website domain, and Google Analytics will only use that cookie data for statistical analysis related to your browsing behavior on that specific website. According to Google, the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains.

If you choose, you can opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser. For more information on Google Analytics, please visit [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/) website.  
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

### **Third-Party Advertisers**

**pixelstalk.net**  serves ads provided by a range of third-party advertising networks. The practices of our advertising partners are not directly covered by **pixelstalk.net** ’s privacy policy. We recommend that you read their policies. For your convenience, we provide a list of our advertising partners below. Unfortunately, we cannot guarantee it is always comprehensive and up to date.

Google, We present you the following information about Google and the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx): Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**pixelstalk.net** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  **pixelstalk.net** ‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or Websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### **Contact Information**

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to **pixelstalk@gmail.com**  for further clarification.
